bizlistdirectory.com 2015-09-14

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Biz List Directory collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.bizlistdirectory.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Biz List Directory.

####  **Registering for an account**

Please note that we are very serious when it comes to privacy and safety of our website users. That's why your account will have to be approved before your listing becomes available in our business directory. The e-mail and URL that you provide to us will be investigated and monitored closely to make sure that you are not a spammer. Please note, when you register for an account on Biz List Directory, and don't add your listing within 48 hours, your account will be deleted from our data base (we do not want to have empty accounts in our data base for more than 48 hours), but you will be able to open a new account in the future using the same e-mail address.

####  **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

####  **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

####  **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

####  **How we use collected information**

Biz List Directory may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  *  _To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently._
  *  _To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services._
  *  _To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site._

####  **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

####  **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

 **ATTENTION NEW USERS!**

As of 06/03/2015 all new users who register on our website; the contact information you provide to us will be available to the public and third parties and it might be used for advertising purposes. 

####  **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

####  **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

####  **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [Google Privacy Ads](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)   

####  **Compliance with children's online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

####  **Changes to this privacy policy**

Biz List Directory has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

####  **Paid Listings and Payment  Policy**

All Biz List Directory users who sign up voluntarily for our Paid Advertising or Classified Packages are required to pay us the full amount for the package they chose when they signed up or when they changed their plan from a Free Package to a Paid Package. The full amount has to be paid on a monthly basis and for as long as their paid listing is active. Biz List Directory has the right to suspend all advertising features if there is an unpaid balance. Users have 5 days after the due date to pay for unpaid invoices.

Biz List Directory users who wants to advertise on our website are voluntarily submitting their payments to Biz List Directory on a monthly basis so they can advertise and keep their ad or classified live on our website. YOU ARE NOT REQUIRED to submit your payment information to Biz List Directory. You will still be able to use our Free Package Features (NO CREDIT CARD REQUIRED).  **Please note:**  you will be limited to some features on our website when you use Free Package Option. 

Biz List Directory is using PayPal when collecting payments from our registered users.([Please read PayPal's Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full#How_you_can_contact_us_about_privacy_questions)). You CAN NOT hold Biz List Directory liable/responsible for any fraudulent transactions caused to the credit card or any personal credit card that was used to pay for the Paid Advertising or Classified Package on Biz List Directory's website. Biz List Directory will only charge the amount you owe for your Paid Advertising or Classified Packages an will collect monthly payments for as long as your Paid Listing is live on Biz List Directory Website.

####  **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

####  **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by e-mail or fill out contact form on our website.

Fill Out [Contact Form](http://bizlistdirectory.com/contact.php)[ ](http://bizlistdirectory.com/contact.php)

Prospect, CT 06712

This document was last updated on June, 03, 2015
